http://www.nintendo.com.au/privacy

Nintendo SwitchWhat is Nintendo Switch?Nintendo Switch gamesGetting Started GuideAccessoriesParental ControlsOnline ServiceamiiboNintendo eShopNintendo 3DSWhat is Nintendo 3DS?Nintendo 3DS gamesNintendo SelectsParental ControlsamiiboNintendo eShopGames for MobileParentsParental ControlsFAQs for ParentsGame classificationsPrivacySupportSupport HomepageService & RepairsCheck Network StatusCustomer ServiceParentsSupportPrivacyNintendo Australia Pty Ltd ACN 060 566 083 (Nintendo) is committed to preserving and respecting the privacy of visitors to this website. Nintendo is not a party to an approved privacy code, but complies with the Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012(the Act) and the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) in relation to the collection, use, security of and access to Personal Information. In this Policy, 'Personal Information' has the same meaning as in the Act.There are no exemptions under the Act which apply to collection of Personal Information on this website.This policy only relates to Personal Information collected on this website.Please read this policy carefully before you use this website or provide any Personal Information. What information is collected?Nintendo will only collect Personal Information from our online visitors to the website for (1) contest registration; (2) newsletter registration; (3) surveys; (4) registration for games or special game-specific promotion participation; (5) and to enable you to join specific groups such as My Nintendo. Personal Information will only be collected with your consent. Personal Information collected may include your name, nickname, e-mail address, mobile phone number and birth date. We do not generally require this information to allow access to this website; however, there may be some areas of the site that you will not be able to access unless you register. For example, "Members Only" areas will require you to register before you can access them.Nintendo also may collect demographic information from visitors, such as age, gender, geographic location, game genre interests, what platforms you own and stores you usually purchase Nintendo products from. This information helps us improve our online offerings and allows us to tailor information to your preferences.Normally, Nintendo does not collect Sensitive Information (as defined in the Act). If Nintendo does collect Sensitive Information, it will only do so with consent, and as specifically permitted by APP 3.3.Back to top What happens to the Personal Information collected?The Personal Information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features and enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, and contests and events of interest. From time to time, Nintendo is approached by companies and organisations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, and we may send out notices on behalf of these companies. We see this as a value-added service helping you to find useful products or services. We strive to limit use of the information you provide to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. You may opt out if you do not wish to receive such material.We may use your Personal Information for internal demographic studies, so we can improve our websites and products to better meet our visitors' needs. In some cases, we may merge your Personal Information with data collected from other sources.Nintendo occasionally uses outside agencies for market research, and may provide these companies with your Personal Information. These companies will be required to comply with Nintendo's privacy practices, the Act and the APPs in handling this information.Nintendo may also disclose Personal Information to government, law enforcement and regulatory bodies where this is necessary for Nintendo to comply with its legal obligations. We will notify you where we are required to make such disclosures. Nintendo may also disclose Personal Information to other organisations with which Nintendo has a business relationship (including other companies within the Nintendo Group provided that such organisations have agreed to treat the Personal Information in accordance with the Act and the APPs).Nintendo may disclose personal information to overseas recipients including Nintendo Co. Ltd (Nintendo’s parent company located in Japan), Nintendo of America Inc. (an affiliated company located in the United States) and Nintendo of Europe GmbH (an affiliated company located in Germany).Back to top A special note about children 13 years old and underNintendo encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. We recognise a special obligation to protect Personal Information obtained from young children. In order for children 13 years old and under to participate in online activities that require registration, we require prior permission from a parent or guardian.Back to top What about cookies?Cookies are files downloaded to your computer to track website browsing behaviour.This website may use cookies to keep track of your choices, or to keep track of the fact that you have signed in so you don't have to continually enter your username and password. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and for other purposes.Back to top Email correspondence to NintendoNintendo may respond to e-mail correspondence if such correspondence includes a return e-mail address. It will retain your email address and other Personal Information contained in any email you send, for that purpose.Back to top Access to and correction of Personal InformationNintendo will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information which Nintendo collects, uses or discloses is accurate, complete and up-to-date.You can obtain details of the Personal Information (such as contact details) that Nintendo hold about you by contacting the numbers below. If you wish to access the information Nintendo holds about you, please send an email or write to our Privacy Compliance Officer (see contact details below) and Nintendo will respond to you within 30 days.You can also request that Nintendo correct or delete Personal Information which it holds about you and in some cases you may be able to change contact details yourself on the website.You can also request details about the way in which Nintendo manages Personal Information.Back to top Safeguarding your Personal InformationNintendo will take reasonable steps to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the Personal Information which it collects. This includes appropriate measures to protect electronic materials and materials in hard copy.Nintendo will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom Nintendo transfers any Personal Information will provide sufficient protection of that Personal Information and as far as possible comply with theAct and the APPs.Back to top Unauthorised Disclosure of Personal InformationIn the event that there is an unauthorised disclosure of Personal Information (whether as a result of accidental disclosure, or malicious conduct by third parties), Nintendo will, as soon as possible, inform you of the nature, content and extent of the unauthorised disclosure, take appropriate remedial steps to prevent further unauthorised disclosures of PersonalInformation, and otherwise comply with all its obligations under the Privacy Act in respect of unauthorised disclosures of Personal Information.Back to top Changes to this PolicyNintendo reserves the right to make changes in or to update this Policy at any time to reflect changes in its business requirements, changes in the law or technological developments. These changes will be displayed on the Nintendo website.Back to top Complaints and further informationIf you have any complaints about Nintendo's privacy practices, would like further information or would like Access to or Correction of your Personal Information, please contact our Privacy Compliance Officer.Our Privacy Compliance Officer will review and investigate your complaint and communicate their findings and any proposed remedial action to you.If you would like a copy of this policy, have any questions, complaints or comments regarding it, or wish to take any of the steps listed above, please contact the Privacy Compliance Officer, Nintendo Australia, 804 Stud Road, Scoresby, Victoria, 3179, e: nintendoaustraliaprivacy@nal.nintendo.com.auBack to top Go BackSectionsWhat information is collected?What happens to the Personal Information collected?A special note about children aged 13 years old and underWhat about cookies?Email correspondence to NintendoAccess to and correction of Personal InformationSafeguarding your Personal InformationUnauthorised Disclosure of Personal InformationChanges to this PolicyComplaints and further informationYou're about to leave nintendo.com.auYou are now leaving nintendo.com.au to an external web site. Nintendo Australia is not responsible for the content or accuracy of any external site.Continue to external siteReturn to nintendo.com.auYou're about to leave nintendo.com.auYou are now leaving nintendo.com.au to an external web site. Nintendo Australia is not responsible for the content or accuracy of any external site.Continue to external siteReturn to nintendo.com.auThank you!We will review and reply as soon as possible lorem ipsum dolor sit amet.Close
